[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
[Geiger counter clicks]
Eh, I'm being squeamish about this.
I have my suit on.
[Geiger counter clicks]
It'll protect me.
I'm just missing the helmet.
[Geiger counter clicks]
So, worst case scenario,
we're only talking brain cancer.
[Geiger counter clicks]
I can live with that.
Actually, that's kind of the point,
[Geiger counter clicks, bullsquid spits]
I CAN live with--
God damn! Get a handkerchief!
[Geiger counter clicks, bullsquid spits]
[Geiger counter clicks, bullsquid moans]
Snot monster!
[Geiger counter clicks]
That's your new name.
But, yeah, unlike my colleagues,
[Geiger counter clicks]
I seem to have a tendency to stay alive.
Since this morning, I've been bitten,
[Geiger counter clicks]
shot,
bombed,
[Geiger counter clicks]
electrocuted,
almost drowned,
[Geiger counter clicks]
almost fallen to my death,
and strangled.
[Geiger counter clicks]
Rasputin wasn't so lucky.
But here I am, exposing myself to radiation.
[Geiger counter clicks]
Why not?
Let's add to the list.
[Geiger counter clicks]
Maybe I can get burned, stabbed, and poisoned
before the day's done.
[Geiger counter clicks]
This is another dead end.
Or maybe it's just flooded
[Geiger counter clicks]
by radioactive green crap.
Oh man, I wonder this is that same spill
[Geiger counter clicks]
from this morning.
That could be seeping everywhere!
I'm not going to drink from the
water fountains anymore.
Oh, hey, this is smart.
This is a great idea!
Yeah, let's crawl into
this drainage pipe!
How could this NOT be the right way?
Actually, I always wished I could
just hop in a giant pneumatic tube
that would take me from my home to work,
or to the liquor store,
the pharmacy,
chemical supply warehouse...
it would be really efficient.
I am a gopher!
[bullsquid spits]
Oh, no, dammit!
Snot rag...
NONE OF YOU ARE HOUSEBROKEN!
[bullsquid groans]
I wonder if this is what
being a dog catcher is like.
Actually, I don't think
they get shotguns.
You probably have to provide your own.
[bullsquid spits]
God... more?!
Eugh!
[bullsquid moans]
This is a pet-trainer's nightmare.
You try and get it to behave and all
it does is puke snot on you and moan.
This looks promising.
I'd like to see a dog catcher
handle this.
If an alien teleported outside,
I could call them up and say,
"Yeah, I got a dog here. He's real mean."
[bullsquids spit, Geiger counter clicks]
Then the catcher would arrive
expecting a dog and get
[bullsquids spit, Geiger counter clicks]
one of these bastards instead.
And he can't just run away because--
[bullsquids spit, Geiger counter clicks]
Dammit.
[Geiger counter clicks]
He can't just run away because technically
his job is animal control,
[Geiger counter clicks]
and this is an animal.
It would be better if you could
[Geiger counter clicks]
get some kids out on the street watching him
so it guilts him into wrestling
[Geiger counter clicks]
with the thing.
Man, I'd videotape that.
[Geiger counter clicks]
This is a lot of radioactive crap.
I bet some people would pay money to get bit
[Geiger counter clicks]
a radioactive alien.
Not me!
[Geiger counter clicks]
I know better!
That always--
[Geiger counter clicks]
pissed me off about Spider-Man,
[bullsquids spit, Geiger counter clicks]
how he got...
NO!
[Geiger counter clicks]
BAD THING!
BAD!
[Geiger counter clicks]
...how Spider-Man got super powers
by bitten by a radioactive...
[Geiger counter clicks]
...spider.
That is such bullshit.
[Geiger counter clicks]
For starters,
the odds of a random mutation
being beneficial are astronomical.
But, more importantly, even
if you did get one,
you'd still have radiation poisoning.
Comic book writers know about as
much about science as I know about...
...well, I'm not a good example
since I know almost everything, but...
the point is, they could try harder.
Hey, I'm up higher.
I wasn't even paying attention.
I wish I could just will myself
out of here like--
[bullsquid grunts]
Daah!
I hate awkward pauses like this.
[bullsquid moans]
Of course, I'm the one who has
to break the ice.
I have to do everything around here.
[houndeye squeals]
Stop that!
Ah hah hah hah!
Today's lesson is on muzzle
energy and momentum.
[houndeye charges up]
Wow, that was fun.
This might my second calling
after physics--shooting stuff?
I don't want to join the
military, though,
because there would always be someone
giving me orders telling me what to shoot.
And they'd want me to lose my beard.
Fuck that.
I don't get what the big deal is with that.
Soldiers had beards in the Civil War,
it worked for them.
[houndeye chirruping]
Oh, I see you.
[explosion]
WHOA!
COMBO PLATTER!
Hope I don't need to go that way.
I wasn't really expecting that to happen.
I DO need to go that way.
Hey! You're hiding!
[houndeye charging up]
I play hide-and-go-seek for keeps.
You should've picked a better spot.
No one hides from me.
[bullsquid spits]
Wow, those snot freaks have good eyesight.
God, I can barely see it.
[bullsquid spits]
Come on!
I need a scoped rifle.
[bullsquid moans]
See, I'm behind the curve on this stuff
because I've never tried
to kill the president.
I've never wanted to.
Because I know as soon as I did,
they'd just replace him with somebody else,
so it's like, what's the point?
Yep, this is the work of that
same catwalk contractor.
Okay, I can jump this.
I'm flying on the wings of radiation.
Yeah.
I wasn't worried about
not making the jump,
but I honestly thought
the platform might
collapse from under me.
[lock buzzes]
That's the kind of day this has been.
RRRRR!
NO!
GOD DAMMIT! THERE'S NOT
EVEN A DOORKNOB!
[metal banging]
Wait, what's that?
What?
I thought I heard somebody
tapping out Morse Code.
Why do I care? I don't even
know Morse Code.
Ngh.
It switched back...
Who are you?
YAH!
Yuck.
[metal banging]
God, what is that noise?
It sounds like the drummer
[metal banging]
to some shitty garage band.
[moaning]
Man, I'm getting old.
This modern day music
[moaning]
just sounds like noise to me.
"Bang bang bang."
[moaning]
It doesn't even have a beat.
[metal banging]
SCIENTIST: Fire the... rocket engine...
SCIENTIST: Destroy the damned thing
[metal banging]
SCIENTIST: before it grows any larger.
SCIENTIST: Dah!
[metal banging]
I know! This music sucks, right?
Don't worry, I'll go make them turn it off.
[moaning]
It's ridiculous.
[metal banging]
Yuck.
God, that's a lot of meat there.
[metal banging]
I wonder how much these things can hold.
Like, if I could a herd a cow in here,
[moaning]
would it be able to lift it all up and eat it?
[metal banging]
It's worth finding out.
[moaning]
[metal banging]
Are you the one making all that noise?
[scientist screams]
MONKEY ON A STICK!
WE'RE GETTING FINGERED BY GODZILLA!
SCIENTIST: NO! NO!
SCIENTIST: GET IT OFF ME!  GET IT OFF!
FUCK!
[scientist screams]
Nnnnghh...
[moaning]
Okay, I was waiting for an
opportunity to use this.
And here it is. It's obvious.
A HANDFUL OF SHRAPNEL
MAKES THE MEDICINE GO DOWN!
[explosion, tentacles moan]
[tentacles moan]
That'll teach you from making so much noise.
You're lucky I don't call the cops,
banging around like you're
more important than me.
What's this? "Test Fire"?
Yes!
[panel buzzes]
[tentacles moans]
Damn...!
I should get out here,
[tentacles moans]
I really wasn't ready for this.
I was expecting some
[tentacles moans]
shitty drummer practicing, or
maybe some scientist into indie music
[tentacles moans]
playing some weird-ass whale song remix,
[metal banging]
but not this.
This is even worse.
[metal banging]
That's not a rope.
You can't fool me.
[metal banging]
Agh, God! Jesus...
It's all over me.
[metal banging]
That's right, the old layer
was starting to dry,
[metal banging]
better baste a new layer of blood on me.
[tentacles moan]
It's important to I maintain
a fresh coat of blood on me at all times.
[tentacles moan]
Helps my sheen.
GUARD: Be quiet! This thing hears us.
[tentacles moan]
I'll say anything damned thing I want.
Whoa.
[tentacles moan]
Don't light a match.
GUARD: HEY!
[tentacles moan]
Hey.
GUARD: HEY, OVER HERE!
[tentacles moan]
I'm behind you.
GUARD: EAT LEAD, YOU OUTER SPACE OCTOP--!
[metal banging]
OH! Shit...!
I'll just...
[metal banging]
Yeah, I'd better chill here for a minute.
[tentacles moan]
I'm going to need some earplugs.